本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作，仅供学习，禁止用于任何商业盈利行为。若因私自散布传播造成法律问题，本字幕组概不负责。更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组。
扫扫加微信
大家字幕组
dajiazimuzu
EVERYONE
关注新浪微博
@大家字幕组
扫扫加微信
很不错哈?
This is nice, huh?
dajiazimuzu
扫扫加微信
大家字幕组
和我的同事们一起享受当之无愧的小憩时光
Taking a well-earned break with my coworkers.
微 信 关 注
dajiazimuzu
我现在感觉自己终于合群了
I feel like I'm finally fitting in here.
这不是你决定的
You don't get to decide when you're fitting in.
而是我们
We'll let you know.
我只是说...我越来越适应这里了
I'm just saying... I'm getting used to it.
还是没适应要站一整天
Not getting used to standing all day.
我就没这麻烦
That's not a problem I have to deal with.
好吧 你真走运 兄弟
Yeah, well, lucky you, my friend.
不是那种好运气.. 不是说你运气好
Not luck-lucky.. not lucky you.
我没有说你很幸运
That's.. I don't think you're lucky.
所以你觉得我很不幸?
So you think I'm unlucky?
不是 好吧 你知道我什么意思
Not, well, you know what I mean.
那只是个口头禅
That's an... it's an expression.
你为啥还不滚?
Why don't you just eject right now?
你说脚疼让我觉得很奇怪
You know, it's so weird that your feet hurt,
因为我感觉每次看见你
because every time I see you,
你都是坐着的
I feel like you're sitting.
试想想怀胎六月还要打这份工什么感觉
Try doing this job six months pregnant.
是的 讲真的 太惨了
Yeah, seriously. That's brutal.
我不知道你也怀孕了
I didn't know you were pregnant too.
我19岁的时候怀过
I was when I was 19.
然后我生了个女儿
Then I gave birth to my daughter.
所以我现在没怀孕了 不过谢谢你这么想
So I'm not pregnant now, but thank you for thinking so.
我不是说你看起来像孕妇
I didn't mean you look pregnant.
- 我的意思是... - 滚蛋 滚蛋!
- I just meant... - Eject. Eject!
我不知道你有孩子
I didn't know that you had a child.
我觉得那很棒
I-listen-that's- I think that's beautiful.
真的 我很敬佩单身妈妈 所以...
Really, I'm in awe of single mothers, so...
我结婚了
I'm married.
你就不该问 老兄
You should've just ejected, man.
你为什么敬佩单身妈妈?
Why are you in awe of single mothers?
我只是觉得--生育孩子需要勇气
I just think it's--it's very brave to have a child,
特别是在你这个年纪
especially at your age.
然而我并没打算要孩子
Well, I didn't set out to have a baby.
意外而已
Came from sex.
好吧 当然
Right. Sure.
呃 不过你很勇敢
Uh, but you--you bravely
决定把孩子生下来
made the decision to go through with it.
那是因为 我没能搭上计划生育组织的便车
Well, I couldn't get a ride to Planned Parenthood.
好吧 如果你以后需要的话可以找我
Well, if you ever need one in the future.
乔纳 我希望
Jonah, I'd prefer
你不是妇科医院派来拉拢
if you didn't offer to shuttle our employees
同事们去堕胎的托
to the abortion clinic.
不是 我是指普通的便车
No, I meant rides in general.
如果是去做巴氏涂片检查呢?
What if it was just for a pap smear?
可以搭便车吗?
Could I get a ride for that?
他们建议我一年去一次 不过我想增加一次
They recommend one a year, but I like to go extra.
确保一切达标
Make sure everything's up to code.
好吧 我只是强调一下
Okay. I'm just gonna say it.
你可以顺道载你的同事去任何地方
I'm fine with you driving your coworkers
除了去妇科医院堕胎
anywhere except the abortion clinic.
见鬼 格林 你不应该在工作场合
Damn it, Glenn, you cannot talk about
谈论你对于堕胎的个人看法
your personal feelings on abortion in the workplace.
- 我可没提堕胎 - 继续说
- I didn't bring up abortion. - Oh, keep tempting me.
- 他说的! - 你逼我记你一笔
- He did! - You are begging me to write you up.
- 没人能阻止我说这个词 - 我会狠狠记你一笔
- I am allowed to say the word. - I will write you up so hard!
堕胎! 堕胎!
Abortion! Abortion!
我要录下这段对话 对着话筒讲
I'm recording this entire conversation. Just speak it in the phone.
堕胎 堕胎 堕胎 堕胎!
Abortion, abortion, abortion, abortion!
谢谢你 你简直作死
Thank you very much. You dug your own grave.
超级商店
第一季 第四集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品
翻译    糖糖   Davion   来福
不可思议 对吧?
It's kind of unbelievable, right?
翻译    糖糖   Davion   来福
他们太像了
They're definitely pretty similar.
翻译     累   Callie   阿克萨鲁
额 我可看不出来
Uh, I don't see it.
翻译     累   Callie   阿克萨鲁
现在我知道为什么你一来
Now I get why you looked familiar
校对    累
我就看你很眼熟了
when you started working here.
校对     累
开始我以为你是
At first, I thought you were
我一个总是反穿着裤子的
this white dude from my middle school
时间轴     西子耶   Papersun
高中白人兄弟
who wore his pants backwards
像克里斯·克罗斯那样 然而并非如此 你是他
like Kris Kross, but nah, you him.
时间轴     西子耶   Papersun
特效     福娃   西子耶
我的意思是
I-I mean,
这不过是个白种男人的人体模特
it's a mannequin of a Caucasian male.
特效     福娃   西子耶
如果你看到我就是这种感觉的话
If that's what you see when you look at me,
压制     冰岛
也许你是着魔了
then maybe this is on you.
压制     冰岛
不不不 没那么简单
Nah, nah, nah, it's more than that.
- 看这眼睛... - 没错
- It's the eyes... - Yeah.
- 鼻子... - 啊哈
- The nose... - Uh-huh.
还有这表情
And there's something about that expression.
让你有种想...
It just kind of makes you want to...
揍他一拳的感觉
Punch him in the face.
有一点
A little bit.
好吧 我没... 好吧 我可没看出来
Yeah, I don't--okay. I'm not seeing any of that.
我看到 我是说
I'm seeing--I mean, what?
他有没有一点像汤姆·克鲁斯 我觉着?
If anything, he looks like Tom Cruise, I guess?
你觉得你像汤姆·克鲁斯?
You think you look like Tom Cruise?
- 这个人体模特 - 某人真是自信心爆棚!
- The mannequin. - Somebody has a healthy ego!
我觉得我像丹泽尔·华盛顿
I guess I look like Denzel Washington.
是啊 我觉得我像莎尔玛·海雅克
Yeah, and I look like Salma Hayek.
走吧丹泽尔
Come on, Denzel.
- 我们回去工作吧 - 好的莎尔玛
- Let's get back to work. - Okay, Salma.
我只是说这个人体模特像
I just meant that's what the mannequin looks
汤姆·克鲁斯...
Tom Cruise...
领养宝宝
真的适合你吗?
把我的宝宝送给陌生人感觉很奇怪
It'd feel weird giving my baby to a stranger,
可是我还没准备好当妈妈
but I also don't know if I'm ready to be a mom.
我懂
I know the feeling.
我生艾玛的时候才19岁
I was 19 when I had Emma.
我都不知道当时我是怎么想的
I had no idea what I was doing.
我只想她过得比我好
I just knew I wanted her to have a better life than me.
是啊
Yeah.
我想 谁知道呢?
I mean, who knows?
也许我的宝宝长大能成为
Maybe my baby could grow up and be
一个经理助理
an assistant manager someday.
是啊 也许你可以更有野心一点
Yeah, or, um, maybe you could dream even bigger.
可经理已经是格林了
Well, Glenn's the manager.
是啊
Yeah.
你也不用急着做决定
Well, you don't have to make the decision anytime soon.
并且如果你想找人聊天 我随时奉陪
And you know that if you want to talk about it, I'm here.
多谢
Thanks.
你也可以跟我聊聊
I'm also here if you want to talk about stuff.
我收养过很多小孩
I've raised a lot of foster children.
哦 好吧 谢谢啦 格林
Oh, okay. Well, thanks, Glenn.
你真好
That means a lot.
还有如果你决定
And if you do decide that adoption
选择找人收养孩子
is the way you want to go
而你觉得交给陌生人很奇怪
and you feel weird about a stranger,
那么 也许乔若莎和我可以收养孩子
well, maybe Jerusha and I could adopt it.
真的吗?
Really?
我们一直都想要个自己的宝宝
We've always wanted a baby of our own.
我是说 收养孩子是一种恩赐
I mean, foster children are a blessing,
可是就好像你一生都在开
but it's as if you've been driving used cars
二手车
your whole life.
如果能体验一次刚出厂的新车
Just once it would be nice to experience a brand-new one,
简直棒呆
straight from the factory,
那车还从未被磕碰过 你懂吗?
that hasn't been all dinged up, you know?
好吧 谢谢你 格林
Okay. Well, thanks, Glenn.
我们会记着的
We'll keep you in mind.
好的
Great.
当然 由你做主
Of course, it's up to you.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
简直和他一毛一样
It looks exactly like him.
噢! 噢 嘿 兄弟 过来认识一下新同事
Oh! Oh, hey, man. Meet our new employee.
乔纳 这是乔纳
Jonah, meet Jonah.
他穿了我的.. 你们给他穿上了我的衣服
He's got my.. You put my clothes on him.
真搞笑 还有名牌 还有...
That's funny. The name tag, and...
所以大家都觉得他和我很像?
So everybody thinks he looks like me?
额 也不是完全一样
Eh, not exactly like you.
你更像是这样
You're a little bit more like,
"嘿 我是乔纳
"Hey, it's me, Jonah.
我爱吃羊角包"
I like to eat croissants."
额 我之前说过这话吗?
Is that something I say?
你大概会这么讲
It sounds like something you would say.
嗯哼 或者是
Yeah, or like,
你看过这个纪录片吗?
Have you seen this documentary?
它会改变你的一生
It will change your life.
还有点英国口音呢
Sounds kind of British.
我装作喜欢爵士乐的样子
I pretend to like jazz,
因为那让我看起来好有修养
because it makes me seem cultured.
我是乔纳 我有特殊的剥香蕉技巧
I'm Jonah. I peel bananas weird.
额 其实那是一个生活小窍门
Well, that's actually a life hack.
香蕉茎秆创造了一个自然而然支撑的枝条
So the stems create a natural holding stick.
这就是为什么猴子们那样剥香蕉
That's why the monkeys do it.
额 这是我在一个 额 纪录片里看到的
It's, um-I saw that in a-in a documentary.
不 亲爱的 这次不再是随随便便领养的孩子了
No, honey, not another foster child.
这次恰恰更会像是我们自己宝贝
This one would be our very own baby.
额 她还不知道是男是女
Well, uh, she doesn't know the sex yet,
不过查宁·塔图姆
but she did have a dream
托梦告诉她 是一个男孩
where Channing Tatum told her it's a boy.
天啊
Oh, my gosh!
传言说有一个婴儿供人竞购
Word on the street is there's a baby up for grabs.
啊? 啊这个
Huh? Oh-oh.
算是吧
Yeah.
我们只是在考虑要不要让人领养这个孩子
We're just thinking, maybe, about adoption.
挺让人为难的
It's a tough call.
我还太年轻 养大一个孩子需要太多责任了
I'm so young, and it's a lot of responsibility,
但同时..
but at the same time..
啊哈 啊哈
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
我愿意加入这场竞争
I'd like to throw my hat in the ring.
你?
You?
是的 从十岁起
Yeah, a baby's been part of my life plan
有个小宝宝就一直是我人生的计划之一
since I was ten.
我有太多太多的爱想给她了
I've got a crap load of love to give.
总之 我的优势如下:
Anyway, here are the facts:
第一 我有一个超舒服的大腿
I have a comfortable lap,
第二 通过拍别人的背部我能让任何一个人打嗝
I can get a burp out of anybody,
第三 因为真菌药物副作用
and I already lactate as a side effect
我已经进入泌乳期了
from some fungal medication I'm taking.
酷啊
Cool.
并不
It is not cool.
说实话 这很恶心而且让我想吐
It is disgusting, if you want to know the truth,
但是在这种情况下可以说是 有用
but in this case, useful.
重点是 过了这村就没这店了
The point is, if you go down the adoption road,
如你选别人收养的话 你会发现他们比我差得远了
you could do a heck of a lot worse than me.
比如说 格林
Like Glenn, for instance.
他弱爆了
He'd be a lot worse.
嘿
Oh, hey.
- 嘿 - 额 我想说
- Hey. - Uh, listen.
关于那个模特的事 真是的是很抱歉
About all that mannequin stuff, sorry.
大家只是找点乐子打发时间
Everyone was just messing around.
我知道了 知道了
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
我就不该有那样的反应的
I shouldn't have even reacted.
我还是个新来的
I'm still new here.
我不想大家因为看到我的表现都觉得我是最敏感的那个
I don't want my thing to be that I'm the sensitive one.
表现?
Your thing?
恩 你懂得 比如
Yeah, like, you know,
加勒特是最酷的
Garrett's the cool one.
格林是老好人
Glenn's the nice one.
夏安是最活泼可爱的
Cheyenne's the perky, sweet one.
卡罗尔是那个最会"贴标签"的
Carol's the one that says "Hashtag" everything.
那我呢
Which one am I?
你 额 是最负责的
You're the, uh, responsible one.
最负责的?
The responsible one?
不不不 褒义的那个意思
In a good way!
你就像兄弟会的看管大妈
You're like the house mom of a frat.
每个人都喜欢她
Everybody loves her.
大家只是不希望她参与到聚会之中来
They just don't expect her to be the life of the party.
拜托 放松点
Oh, come on. Lighten up.
我只是说你一直不像
I'm just saying you're not, like,
一个会乱开玩笑的人呀
one to joke around all the time.
我想说的是 至少我也可以偶尔被取笑一下吧
I mean, at least I can take a little bit of teasing.
我也可以啊
I can take teasing.
- 真的吗? - 当然
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
我有一个哥哥
I had older brothers.
反正他开我玩笑 我根本不在乎的
I-teasing does not faze me.
真的? 根本不在乎?
Oh, teasing doesn't even faze you?
一点都不 真的 我一点问题都没有
No, it doesn't at all. I'm fine with it.
- 那很好 - 是啊
- Oh, good. - Yeah.
幸好你告诉我了
That's good to know.
是挺好的
It is good to know.
额 为什么是幸好知道?
Wh-why is that good to know?
你到底知道了什么?
What do you know?
你在诱引熊吗?
You baited the bear, huh?
没关系的
It's fine.
我觉得很有趣
I think it's funny.
哥根本不在乎
It's fine. I'm fine.
一点都不
This is fine.
他为什么这么拿香蕉?
Why is he holding the bananas wrong?
就该这么拿 其实人类都拿错了!
It's humans that hold them wrong!
好了
Okay.
我想我们的公主派对必需品已经齐啦
I think that is all of our princess party supplies.
祝你的猫能过一个美妙的生日
I hope your cat has a wonderful birthday.
这也能算是戏弄吗?
Call that teasing?
花样滑冰可是
Because figure skating
体育竞技中的为数不多的艺术呢
is one of the few sports that is also an art.
真是谢谢您嘞
So, if anything, thank you.
放着我来
Let me help you with that.
谢谢你啦
Oh, thank you.
你可能怀着我的孩子呢
You might be carrying my baby.
或者是迪娜的
Yeah, yours or Dina's.
什么?
What?
迪娜说她也对
Dina said she might be interested
领养我的孩子有兴趣
in adopting my baby too.
迪娜? 真的吗?
Dina? Really?
好吧 做你认为是最正确的
Well, whatever you think is best.
别有压力
Don't stress.
对孩子不好
Bad for baby.
爱你哦妈咪
I love you, Mommy.
你的宝宝哭的时候 你就是这么对待他的吗?
So that's what you would do if your baby cried, huh?
看来你听说了
Oh, I guess you've heard
我要领养夏安的宝宝的事了
I'll be raising Cheyenne's child.
做梦吧你
Oh, the "H" you will.
你对婴儿一点都不了解
You don't know the first thing about babies.
你知道怎么给宝宝裹毯子吗?
Do you even know how to swaddle?
我曾经在快餐店兼职
I used to work part-time at Chipotle.
跟摊玉米饼是一个道理
Same principle as a burrito.
不过就是不同的手法
Different wrapper and different fillings.
总之 养孩子是一种本能
Anyway, parenting's just about instincts.
我的本能已经养成多年了 大姐
Oh, I've got instincts for days, lady.
我的本能已经要溢出来了
I've got instincts up the W-A-Z-O-O.
真的吗?
Oh, really?
那是你的宝宝
That was your baby.
她刚摔成脑震荡了
She just got a concussion.
啥? 那都不是个真的...
What? That's not even a real...
啊呀 头骨骨折
Oops. Skull fracture.
好吧 这是有区别的...
Okay, there's a difference between...
别再伤害我的宝宝了!
you stop hurting my baby!
然后真的乔纳
And then real Jonah
站在新娘乔纳旁边
was standing next to bride Jonah,
看起来就像是真的乔纳
and it looked like real Jonah
在从大猩猩手里抢走新娘乔纳
was giving bride Jonah away to the gorilla.
真棒
Amazing.
好好笑
So funny.
加勒特 你去做换班安排吧
Garrett, finish the shift assignments.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
今天真是太有趣了
I love today.
大家字幕组
我可以做换班安排
I mean, I could do the shift assignments,
也可以坐这里吃我的通心粉
or I could finish eating my mac and cheese.
大家字幕组
你猜我选哪个
I wonder what I'll do.
- 我能... - 你来吧
- Could... - Go on.
雷吉 让你那么诡异地看我
Reggie, thanks for looking at me weird.
希望你喜欢鲜肉冷冻室
I hope you like the meat freezer.
好了 换班安排
Okay. Shift assignments.
玛姬 今天早上
Margie, who shushed me
在我唱歌的时候叫我安静
this morning when I was singing.
真是巧了
Oh, look.
你要去冷冻室卸货了
You are unpacking stock in the freezer.
德里克 也去冷冻室
Derek, also in the freezer.
瑞贝卡 让你高冷 化妆品区
Rebecca, who is icy to me, cosmetics.
开玩笑的!
Kidding!
冷冻室!
Freezer!
请问 艾米在哪?
Um, where's Amy?
艾米忙着呢
Amy is busy.
你因为这个问题也要去冷冻室啦
And you just talked your way into the freezer.
我喜欢时不时的和我的员工
I love to get together with my employees
还有他们的宝贝爸爸聚一聚
and their baby daddies from time to time.
这样我们可以互相的
You know, just so we can all get to know each other
了解对方多一点
a little bit better.
好啊 联络感情 不错
Yeah, networking. Nice.
哥们咱聊起哟
Let's link it in, G.
真抱歉我桌子上这么乱
Listen I apologize for the mess on my desk.
这么多家庭照片 你瞧见没?
So many family photos, you know?
这张是我和孩子们在沙滩上照的
Oh, here's one of me and my kids at the beach.
真是值得分享的回忆啊
Such a--such a special moment to share.
哇! 这椅子还有轮子?
Whoa! This chair's got wheels?
哎呦喂! 兄弟混的不错啊!
Damn, son! Living large. What's up?
谢谢
Thank you.
格林 如果你是想
Glenn, if you're trying
通过这种方式让我们选你不选迪娜 那...
to get us to choose you over Dina, then...
没有的事!
Not at all!
这完全取决于你们啊 对吧?
I mean, it's entirely up to you guys, right?
咱这是聊啥呢?
Well, what are we talking?
什么?
Excuse me?
你懂的 票票
You know, like skrilla.
不好意思 什么是...
I'm sorry, what is...
就是钱
That means money.
小博 咱们不能这样把自己的孩子卖了
Bo, I don't think we should sell our baby.
要是你的主意你就会喜欢了
You'd like it if it was your idea.
该死的警报器!
Aw, French fudge! Um...
失陪了 我得去看看
I'm sorry. I have to look into that.
但我很愿意再谈谈钱的问题 你懂的...
Uh, but I'd be happy to, uh, you know, discuss bribe money...
票票啥的
and skrilla.
- 好的 - 票票事宜?
- Yeah. - Bribe skrilla?
别别别! 别这样!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! No! Come on!
拜托!
Please!
快停下!
Stop it! Come on!
没事儿 大家伙
Everything's fine, guys.
没事的 放松 都退后
It's fine. Relax. Back up.
警报声意味着东西装太满了
The alarm means it's too full!
机器有点卡住了 我只要...
The machine's just a little stuck, and I've got to...
- 只需要把它塞进去... - 你干了什么?
- Just need to get this into the... - What--what have you done?
格林! 我很抱歉
Glenn! Every--I'm so sorry.
- 上帝啊! - 我不是...
- Oh, God! - I-no-I didn't...
天哪! 那是谁?
Oh, God! Who is that?
不! 你这个禽兽!
No! You monster!
没事的 那谁也不是
It's nothing. It's nobody.
你这个刽子手! 你干了什么?
You monster! What have you done?
不是那样的 格林!
No, Glenn!
天哪!
Oh, God!
我们就只是问一些问题
We're just gonna ask you a few questions
来了解你们会是怎样的家长
to learn more about what kind of parents you'd be,
所以回答没有对错
so there's no right or wrong answers.
对 只要用心回答就行了
Yeah, just speak from the heart, yo.
好  第一个问题
Okay. First question.
你们是不是恋童癖?
Are you a pedophile?
- 不 - 绝对不是
- No. - Definitely not.
挺好的
Nice.
目前打平
So far it's a tie.
- 我扔掉人体模型
- I was trying to get rid of the mannequin
只是因为它让我心烦意乱
because it was becoming a distraction.
-承认吧 我的恶作剧成功了
Just admit that my fun pranks got to you,
可能你就是那种很敏感的人吧
and that maybe you're the sensitive one.
不 在变敏感和被恼怒了之间
No, there's a difference between being sensitive
是有区别的
and being annoyed.
你会懂的
You would understand
如果有人对你做了同样的事情
if someone did the same thing to you.
什么鬼?
What?
艾米 你在干嘛?
Amy, what are you doing here?
不
No.
乔纳,这一点都不像我
Jonah, that looks nothing like me.
看上去我戳到你痛处了，是不是?
Looks like I touched a nerve, huh?
看看这个
Hey, look at this.
看看这个这个"艾米"在干嘛
What is Amy doing here?
- 这个模型是艾米? - 是啊!
- That's supposed to be Amy? - Yeah!
真是一个悲伤的故事
So sad.
你紧紧抓住了
Well, you totally nailed
这个6尺高，金发这些特征啊
the whole six foot tall, blonde hair thing.
这是我能找到的最好的了
It's the best that I could find.
或者 换做艾米会说...
Or, as Amy would say...
我现在大脑一片空白
I'm totally blanking right now.
你走吧 走走走走走
You go. Go, go, go, go, go.
走吧
Go.
"我看上去像一个普通白人女孩?"
"I look like a random white girl"?
呵呵
Mm, nice try.
为了知道我的孩子的生活
To get a sense of what our child's life
在你们的陪伴下会是怎样的
would be like with you,
我想了解一下你们的邻居
what's your neighborhood like?
尖篱笆围墙 名校环绕
Picket fences. Good schools.
你知道"Los Guapos"这帮派吗?
Are you familiar with a gang called "Los Guapos"?
我那是他们的领地 但是 呃
It's their turf, but, uh,
我们达成了协议
we have an understanding.
我觉得对我的孩子也会生效的
So I assume that would extend to my baby as well.
好吧 所以如果一个小孩
Okay, so if a baby
便便了 你们会
does poo-poo, would you, like,
从前往后擦还是从后往前擦
wipe it front to back or back to front?
前 从后往前
Front--back to front.
从前往后 从前往后
Front to back. Front to back.
- 真是够业余的 - 最终答案!
- What an amateur. - Final answer!
不 呃 男孩还是女孩?
No. Uh, boy or girl?
嗯 记下来 这要加分
Yeah, write that. That was good.
好的吧 那么 呃
Okay, so, uh,
假设一下情景
I'ma throw you, like, a hypothetical.
你在房间中跳舞
Let's say you're, like, dancing around the room,
然后突然间 踢到了宝宝的脸
and accidentally, you kick the baby in the face.
你怎么道歉?
How do you say you're sorry about that?
嗨 主管
Yo, chief.
加勒特
Hey, Garrett.
看这个
Check it out.
鲨鱼攻击
Shark attack.
这不赖啊
Ooh, that's great. Hey.
我觉得要告诉你一下
I thought that you should know that
没人管理那个试衣间了
there's nobody to let anyone in the dressing rooms,
那变得有点怪怪的
and it's starting to get a little weird.
贝蒂呢?
Well, where is Betty?
贝蒂说了
Yeah, Betty had said
一些Lady Gaga不好的东西
something critical about Lady Gaga,
所以马特奥让她去冷库了
so Mateo assigned her to freezer duty.
你知道么?
Well, you know what?
那换其他人来吧
Let somebody else fix it for once.
这是你的错
This is your fault.
你才是那个玩忽职守的那个
You're the one that outsourced your job
因为你一直忙于工作中调情
cause you're busy with a work flirt.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
什么? 工作调情? 是啥意思?
What? Work flirt? What does that even mean?
每个人都会做 你在工作中小小的调个情
Everybody does it. You flirt a little bit at work.
- 来混时间 - 不
- Pass the time. - No.
我在任何时间
I got, like, five or six work flirts going on
都有五六个调情对象
at any given time.
嗨 詹尼弗 怎么样啊?
Hey, Jennifer. What it do, Boo?
嗯 这对你来说挺好的，加勒特
Well, that's great for you, Garrett,
但我没这么做
but that is not what is happening.
我没在和乔纳调情
I am not flirting with Jonah.
这仅仅是因为乔纳说
This is because Jonah said
我是那个"负责"的人
that I was the responsible one.
- 不会吧 - 是的
- No. - Yes.
- 他说你 "负责"?
- He called you responsible?
可笑吧
I know.
好吧 那我能理解
Well, then I completely understand
为什么你把鲨鱼
why you are attaching a shark
和一个人体模型的断腿放在一起了
to the severed leg of a mannequin.
我认为我作为父母的一个最重要的品质就是
I think my best quality as a parent is that
我是一个稳重的 有爱心的 已婚男人
I'm a stable, loving, married man.
所以我才没有一堆奇怪的男人
So I don't have groups of strange men
每晚都来我家鬼混
wandering through my house every night.
只有一个男的 自从我装上门栓就没再发生了
It was one man, and not since I installed the deadbolt.
你就是个栓
Your brain's a deadbolt.
是啊 至少我没有培养出
Yeah, well at least I don't have foster children
进监狱的孩子
that I raised currently in prison.
那只是少管所
It's a juvenile correctional facility.
看吧 我觉得你们要扪心自问了
Look, I guess you just have to ask yourselves,
你是希望你的孩子
do you want your child raised in a home with loaded handguns
在"枪林弹雨"中成长?
laying around?
还是你希望你的孩子能由格林来抚养?
Or do you want your child raised by Glenn?
别指着我
Do not point at me.
我会双倍奉还
I'll point two fingers back at you.
- 你才不敢呢 - 噢 是吗? 哈哈!
- You wouldn't dare. - Oh, yeah? Ha-ha!
- 你知道吗? - 看到没?
- Okay, you know what? - See?
这违反了员工守则
That's a violation of the code of conduct.
- 这就违规了? - 这他妈当然是了
- Oh, is it a violation? - It sure as heck is.
- 真的吗? - 没错
- Oh, really? - Yep.
- 谁规定的? - 老娘我!
- Who put that in there? - I did!
我说了我很抱歉 你还想干嘛?
I said I'm sorry. What else do you want?
只是到处说这类东西
It's just careless
实在是不负责了
to go around saying things like that.
流言蜚语就是这么传出去的
This is how rumors get started.
我只是说你有点调情的味道
I was just saying you were being a little flirty.
我又没说你们你们在休息室打炮
I didn't say you were banging in the break room.
给点力啊!
Come on! Help me out here.
卧槽!
Whoa!
呃 嗨 伙计们
Oh, hey, guys.
流言就是这么传出去的
Now, that is how rumors get started.
事情不是你们看到这样
This is not how it looks.
是吗?
Really?
看起来像你买了一个充气娃娃
Cause it looks like you got a sex doll
然后你把她打扮成艾米那样
and you dressing it up to look like Amy.
- 是的 - 不是的
- Yeah. - No.
这听起来有点像跟踪狂
See, that sounds stalker-y,
我特意买这个娃娃
whereas I specifically bought this doll
因为她本来就很像艾米
because it already looked like Amy.
我要走了
I'm walking away.
这下好了 人越来越多了
Oh, good. More people.
- 我的天啊! - 那是艾米吗?
- Oh, my God! - Is that supposed to be Amy?
- 不是 - 是的 是的
- No. - Yes, yes.
我想要报复艾米
I wanted to get back at Amy,
但是商店里的人体模型
and there are no mannequins in the store
没有一个有一丁点像她的
that look remotely like her.
关于这个人体模型的事 我能多嘴问一句吗?
Which, can we talk about that for a second?
为什么没有西班牙或者拉美籍的人体模型?
Why are there no Spanish/Latina themed mannequins?
不 不 不 我们先不谈那个
Oh, no, no, no, we not talking about that.
我们来谈谈眼前的这个模型
Let's talk about this.
乔纳 发生什么事了?
Jonah, what is happening?
你收藏了我们每个人的娃娃吗?
Do you own one of each of us?
当然没有!
No!
午饭时候我去了很多商店
I went to a bunch of different stores over lunch,
然后我碰巧路过一家情趣用品店
and then I just happened to pass this in the window
发现这个娃娃看着像艾米
of a sex shop, and look, it looks just like Amy.
真的像
Yeah, it does.
乔纳 你能把那个地方遮挡一下吗?
Jonah, can you cover that up, please?
这样很不得体
It's completely inappropriate.
- 问题解决了 - 你开什么玩笑?
- Problem solved. - Are you kidding me?
这不是你们想象那样的
This is not a sexual thing.
艾米 你的屁股很不错哦
Amy, you've got a good butt.
夏安?
Cheyenne?
额 之前我们把事情
We, uh-we let things
搞得一团糟
get a little out of hand before.
但重要的是
The important thing is,
不管发生什么 我们都会在这里
we are here for you no matter what,
只要是一切为你孩子好的事
and we want to do whatever's best
我们都愿意做
for your child.
所以我们同意
So that's why we've agreed
共同拥有对孩子的监护权
to share custody.
- 什么? - 你没听错
- Huh? - Yeah.
我们将在晚上和周末轮流照顾孩子
We're gonna alternate nights and weekends.
是的 如果我俩都工作得很晚
Yeah, and if both of us have to work late,
那么其他人可以把孩子带回家
then someone else can go home with it.
乔纳 艾米
Jonah. Amy.
加勒特 我们都可以轮流来照顾的
Garrett. We'd all trade off.
像班级里的仓鼠一样
Like the class hamster
每个孩子都轮流照顾它
each child gets a turn taking care of,
这样你的孩子就成了店里大家的孩子
this would be kind of the store baby.
没错
Exactly.
谢谢你们
Thank you so much,
但是我和小博还是想自己抚养孩子
but I think Bo and I are gonna keep it.
你确定吗?
You sure?
想想什么才是对宝宝最好的
Think what's best for the baby.
我现在做的就是对宝宝最好的
That's what I'm doing.
你知道吗?
And you know what?
我觉得我们能自己抚养孩子的
I think we're gonna be fine.
那这样说来 今天就是在浪费我的时间
So this whole day was a waste of my time, then.
嘿 碰上你太好了
Hey. Glad I caught you.
这是什么?
What is this?
是一张收据
That is a receipt,
证明我已经退掉充气娃娃了
which is proof that I returned the doll.
你付了400刀的手续费
You paid a $400 restocking fee.
是的 比买个新娃娃还要贵
Yeah, it was actually more than the doll cost.
额 显然二手充气娃娃
Um, apparently there's not
没有什么市场需求
a huge after market for used sex dolls.
不管怎样 我终于明白今天是怎么一回事了
Anyway, I figured out what today was really about.
你发现了?
You did?
加勒特和你说了?
Did Garrett talk to you?
别听他的 那太扯了
Because that is ridiculous.
那不是我们..
That is not what we..
你只是在捉弄新人
You were hazing me.
是的
Yeah.
是的 捉弄
Yeah, hazing.
我们谁都会捉弄
That's.. it's what we do to everybody.
我承认 被你打败了
You got me. You got me.
事情虽然有点失控
I mean, it got a little out of control,
但是你通过了考核
but you passed.
我通过了! 我通过了入会仪式
I passed! I passed the initiation.
恭喜你
Congrats.
那 我现在是商店的一份子了
So I'm, uh, part of the group now.
- 是的 正式欢迎你 - 谢谢
- Yep, welcome, officially. - Thank you.
那我们明天见咯
I'll, uh.. I'll see you tomorrow.
是的 明天会见到大家的
Yep, we'll see everyone tomorrow.
婴儿床在这
Right there, big ol' wheels.
哦 这张很不错啊
Oh, this could be bangin'.
- 这张怎么样 - 不错
- How about this one? - Oh, yeah.
你知道吗 我们可以把它弄得更棒
We trick this thing out right, you know?
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
让我叔叔在两边刷上漆
Get my uncle to throw some tint up on the sides here,
大家字幕组
这样就不会有人
so we don't have, like, people peeping in
偷窥小冬瓜的秘密了
on shorty's little business going on here?
爸爸就在这
Big Daddy in the house, right here.
大家字幕组
小胖在旁边
Shorty by the side.
往后退一点 我们开车兜兜风
Stand back. We're taking this for a ride.
哟 Wagwan Selecta
Yo, Wagwan, Selecta,
不知不觉影响我们 侵蚀我们的心灵
dissin' our mind, corruption and don't you know here.
对 呸
Yeah. Boo
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140
成为父亲真的...
Being a dad and...
怎样?
What's up?